Here you go.
幹得好。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Say Rachel, I was wondering if you'd like to go to a movie with me sometime.
比如說雷切爾，我想知道你是否願意找個時間跟我一起去看電影。
As my lover.
作為我的愛人。
Too out there.
太外面了。
Maybe you'd just like to get something to eat with me sometime.
也許你只是想找個時間和我一起吃點東西。
As my lover.
作為我的愛人。
Hi.
你好。
All right.
好的。
Let's go shopping.
我們去購物吧。
I've got a positive balance on my credit card and I want to use it up before Citibank
我的信用卡有正餘額，我想在花旗銀行之前用完它
goes under.
下去了。
Good idea.
好主意。
Before we go, you know, there's something I need to say.
在我們離開之前，你知道，我有話要說。
Oh.
哦。
Okay.
好的。
I've kind of had this crush on you.
我有點迷戀你了。
But since you're with Ross, I didn't do anything about it.
但既然你和羅斯在一起，我就沒有做任何事。
But now that you're not, I'd really like to ask you out sometime.
但現在你不在了，我真的很想找個時間約你出去。
So that's what I'm doing now.
這就是我現在正在做的事情。
Wow.
哇。
Um.
嗯。
I dropped a cup.
我掉了一個杯子。
Yeah, I know.
是的，我知道。
I'll be there for you
我會在你身邊
I'll be there for you too
我也會在你身邊
It'll understand you, but it's going to make fun of you
它會理解你，但會取笑你
Oh, this is so great
哦，這太棒了
Yeah, it was
是的，那是
Alright then
那麼好吧
Bye
再見
Hello, people who do not live here
您好，不住在這裡的人們
Hello
你好
I gave you a key for emergencies
我給了你一把緊急鑰匙
We were out of Doritos
我們已經沒有多力多滋了
Hey, how'd the date go with Mr. Millionaire?
嘿，和百萬富翁先生的約會怎麼樣？
Mr. Millionaire, new from Snooty Playthings
百萬富翁先生，Snooty Playthings 的新成員
Third wife, sold separately
第三任妻子，單獨販售
He's great
他很棒
I mean, we have such a good time together
我的意思是，我們在一起度過了一段美好的時光
He's so funny and so sweet
他是如此有趣又如此甜蜜
And I'm not attracted to him at all
我對他一點興趣都沒有興趣
Still?
仍然？
No, it's driving me crazy
不，這讓我發瘋
I mean, in every other way, he's like the perfect guy
我的意思是，從其他方面來看，他都是一個完美的人
He has everything
他擁有一切
Plus, he actually has everything
另外，他實際上擁有一切
Life-sized Imperial Stormtroopers from Sharper Image?
Sharper Image 中的真人大小的帝國衝鋒隊？
Two
兩個
Wow, can Joey and I put them on and fight?
哇，我和喬伊可以穿上它們去戰鬥嗎？
Oh, mommy
哦，媽媽
Oh, daddy
哦，爸爸
I am a big old daddy
我是一個大爸爸
Oh, mommy
哦，媽媽
Oh, daddy
哦，爸爸
I am a big old daddy
我是一個大爸爸
I guess he must have gotten the part in that play
我想他一定得到了那齣戲的角色
Yeah, either that or Gloria Estefan was right
是的，無論是那個還是格洛麗亞·埃斯特凡都是對的
Eventually, the rhythm is going to get you
最終，節奏會讓你
Joe, how's it going?
喬，怎麼樣？
Good
好
Hey
嘿嘿
Hi
嗨
Oh, so you're playing Adrian, huh?
哦，所以你在扮演阿德里安，是嗎？
Yes
是的
Are you one of the retarded cousins?
你是智障表兄弟之一嗎？
Oh, no
哦，不
I'm playing your husband, Victor
我扮演你的丈夫，維克多
I'm Joey Tribbiani
我是喬伊·崔比亞尼
Hi, nice to meet you, Kate Miller
你好，很高興認識你，凱特米勒
So, the play's pretty great, huh?
這麼說來，這部劇還是很精彩的吧？
Oh, yeah
哦，是的
I love Jennifer Benberry's work
我喜歡詹妮弗·本伯裡的作品
She's so brilliantly incisive when it comes to deconstructing the psyche of the American middle class
她在解構美國中產階級的心理方面表現得非常敏銳
Oh, forget about it
噢，忘了它吧
She rocks
她搖滾
Where do I know you from?
我從哪裡認識你？
Dr. Drake Remore
德雷克·雷摩爾博士
Days of Our Lives
我們生命中的日子
Voted most dateable neurosurgeon by Teen Beat
被 Teen Beat 評選為最適合約會的神經外科醫生
No, that's not it
不，不是這樣的
So, you're a soap actor
所以，你是肥皂剧演員
Well, this must be pretty exciting for you, being in a real play, huh?
嗯，這對你來說一定很令人興奮，在一場真正的戲劇中，對吧？
Hey, I've done plays before
嘿嘿，我以前演過戲
I'm a serious actor
我是一個認真的演員
That infomercial
那個電視廣告
For the milk carton spout thing
對於牛奶盒噴嘴的事情
You're the guy who doesn't know how to pour milk
你就是那個不會倒牛奶的傢伙
See, I actually can pour milk
你看，我真的可以倒牛奶
But I got you believing that I couldn't
但我讓你相信我做不到
Now, see, that's acting
現在看，這就是演技
Right, at the end you choked on a cookie
是的，最後你被餅乾噎住了
Yeah, that was real
是的，那是真的
Wow, I cannot believe Mark asked you out
哇，我不敢相信馬克約你出去
I know
我知道
So, what are you gonna tell him?
那麼，你要告訴他什麼呢？
Well, I told him I would think about it
嗯，我告訴他我會考慮一下
But I'm gonna tell him no
但我要告訴他不
Huh
呵呵
I mean, I think I'd say no to anybody right now
我的意思是，我想我現在會對任何人說不
Oh, but it was so strange
哦，但這太奇怪了
I mean, I'm standing there with this charming, cute guy
我是說，我和這個迷人可愛的傢伙站在一起
Who's asking me to go out with him
誰叫我跟他出去
Which I'm allowed to do
我可以這樣做
And I felt guilty
我感到內疚
You know, like I'd be cheating on Ross or something
你知道，就像我會欺騙羅斯什麼的
Wow, so?
哇，所以？
Okay, maybe that means that you're not over Ross yet
好吧，也許這意味著你還沒有忘記羅斯
And you have issues with your father
你和你父親之間也有問題
I don't have any issues with my father
我和父親沒有任何問題
Okay, so it's probably just the Ross thing then
好吧，那麼這可能只是羅斯的事情
I hate this woman, I hate her
我討厭這個女人，我討厭她
She told everyone in the company about that infomercial
她向公司裡的每個人講述了那個電視廣告
And now they all keep asking me to open their drinks
現在他們都一直要我開啟他們的飲料
Okay, and whenever I can't do it
好吧，每當我做不到的時候
They're all like, like laughing at me
他們都像在嘲笑我
Hello
你好
Hey
嘿嘿
So, Rachel called
於是，雷切爾打電話給
Wants to see me
想見我
Going over in a minute
一分鐘就過去了
Wow, well, what do you think she wants?
哇，好吧，你認為她想要什麼？
Well, maybe the crazy fog has lifted
好吧，也許瘋狂的迷霧已經散去
And she realizes that life without me
她意識到沒有我的生活
Sucks
糟透了
It's possible
這是可能的
You are very lovable
你很可愛
I'd miss you if I broke up with you
如果我跟你分手我會想念你
He's just trying to be supportive
他只是想提供支援
He'll be supportive like a guy
他會像個男人一樣支援
If I broke up with you, I'd miss you
如果我跟你分手，我會想念你
Hi
嗨
You, uh, wanted to see me?
你，呃，想見我嗎？
Yeah
是啊
Uh, here's a box of your stuff
呃，這是你的東西盒
What?
什麼？
Uh, you know, it's just like hats and shirt and CDs
呃，你知道，它就像帽子、襯衫和 CD
Just sort of stuff that you've left here
只是你留在這裡的一些東西
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Are you trying to hurt me or something?
你是想傷害我還是怎麼的？
No
否
Ross, if you...
羅斯，如果你...
It just seems that, you know, it's time we, you know, move on
看來，你知道，是時候我們，你知道，繼續前進了
I mean, don't you think?
我的意思是，你不覺得嗎？
Yes
是的
Yeah
Yes, I do
是的，我願意
Good
好
Yeah, I really do
是的，我真的願意
Hey
嘿嘿
This, this was a gift
這，這是一份禮物
Ross, you got that for free from the museum gift shop
羅斯，你從博物館禮品店免費得到的
It's still a gift
這仍然是一份禮物
I got it from the gift shop
我從禮品店買的
Okay, all right, give me the mug, I'll keep the mug
好吧，好吧，把杯子給我，我會保留杯子
No
否
You know, you know, don't do me any favors
你知道，你知道，別幫我任何忙
In fact, where...
事實上，哪裡...
Where's the rest of my stuff?
我剩下的東西在哪裡？
Huh? Like, like my, um...
啊？就像，就像我的，嗯...
Hey
嘿嘿
This book is mine
這本書是我的
And, and, and, and that T-shirt you sleep in
還有、還有、還有你睡覺時穿的那件 T 恤
I'd like that back too
我也想要回來
Yes, I do
是的，我願意
You know how much I love that T-shirt
你知道我有多喜歡那件 T 卹
You never even wear that T-shirt
你甚至從來沒有穿過那件T卹
I'm just trying to help you move on
我只是想幫助你繼續前進
Oh, you are a petty man
哦，你是個小人
You are a petty, petty, petty, petty small...
你真是個小人，小人，小人，小人……
You are so just doing this out of spite
你這樣做只是出於惡意
No, no, no
不，不，不
I'm gonna wear this all the time
我會一直穿著這個
I love this shirt
我喜歡這件襯衫
You have not worn that T-shirt since you were 15
你從 15 歲起就沒有穿過那件 T 卹了
It doesn't even fit you anymore
它甚至不再適合你了
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊。
Oh, okay, okay.
噢，好吧，好吧。
If you don't mind, I'm going to take the rest of my stuff
如果你不介意的話，我會帶走我剩下的東西
and relax
並且放鬆
in my favorite shirt.
穿著我最喜歡的襯衫。
You have a pleasant evening.
您度過了一個愉快的夜晚。
So you're, like, a zillionaire.
所以你就像是個億萬富翁。
And you're our age. You're our age.
而你也到了我們這個年紀。你已經是我們這個年紀了
You know what? You should, like, you should buy a state
你知道嗎？你應該，就像，你應該買一個州
and then just name it after yourself.
然後以你自己的名字命名。
What, like, Pete, Dakota?
什麼，比如皮特，達科他？
Yeah, or Mississippi-te.
是的，或者密西西比州。
Oh, oh, I got it.
哦，哦，我明白了。
Pete, Chicago.
皮特，芝加哥。
That's not a state, Joe.
那不是一個州，喬。
Oh, and Mississippi-te is?
哦，密西西比州是嗎？
I gotta go, so, uh,
我得走了，所以，呃，
I'll see you guys later.
稍後再見。
Okay, you're our age.
好吧，你已經到了我們這個年紀了。
So, uh, we on for tomorrow?
那麼，呃，我們明天繼續？
Absolutely.
絕對地。
Now get out of here, you!
現在離開這裡，你！
Okay, I'm running out of places I can touch him.
好吧，我已經沒有地方可以碰他了。
Is there something wrong with me?
我是不是有什麼問題啊？
I mean, why am I only attracted to guys
我的意思是，為什麼我只被男人吸引
where there's no future?
哪裡沒有未來？
Either they're too old, or they're too young,
要嘛太老，要嘛太年輕
or they're a big, misogynist, jerk poet like Julio,
或者他們是像胡裡歐那樣的大塊頭、厭女的混蛋詩人，
who, by the way, I'm still attracted to.
順便說一句，我仍然被他所吸引。
And then there's Pete, who's crazy about me.
還有皮特，他對我很著迷。
I mean, he's absolutely perfect,
我的意思是，他絕對完美，
and there's, like, zip going on.
還有，就像，拉鍊正在進行中。
I mean, seriously, does it sound like
我的意思是，說真的，這聽起來像是
there's something wrong with me?
我有什麼問題嗎？
Yeah, kinda.
是的，有點。
Happy? Is that what I'm supposed to be, Vic?
快樂的？這就是我該做的事嗎，維克？
Happy?
快樂的？
Well, why don't you tell me
好吧，為什麼不告訴我
what you're supposed to be, huh?
你應該是什麼樣子，對吧？
Because I sure as hell can't figure it out.
因為我確實無法弄清楚。
I talk to you, and nothing.
我和你說話，什麼都沒有。
You look at me, and it's nothing.
你看著我，什麼都不是。
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
Tasty.
可口。
I'm really starting to feel
我真的開始感覺到
like you guys have a history.
就像你們有歷史一樣。
It's nice.
很好。
I have a question about this scene.
我對這個場景有一個疑問。
Yes.
是的。
Well, I don't understand
嗯，我不明白
why Adrian's attracted to Victor.
為什麼阿德里安會被維克多吸引。
Peel the onion.
洋蔥去皮。
First of all, he's good-looking.
首先，他長得好看。
Yeah.
是的。
I think my character's gonna need
我想我的角色需要
a little bit more of a reason than that.
比這多一點的原因。
Oh, hey, how about this one?
哦，嘿，這個怎麼樣？
Uh, it says so in the script!
呃，劇本裡面是這麼說的！
You know, uh, I don't know
你知道，呃，我不知道
why my character likes you, either.
為什麼我的角色也喜歡你。
I mean, it says in the script here
我的意思是，這裡的指令碼中說
that you're a bitch.
你是個婊子。
It doesn't say that in the script.
劇本裡並沒有這麼說。
It does in mine.
我的也是如此。
I can blow-dry it.
我可以吹乾它。
I can put gel on it.
我可以把凝膠塗在上面。
It doesn't matter.
沒關係。
I still wind up
我還是結束了
with this little cowlicky thing
和這個可笑的小東西
on the middle part of my head.
在我頭的中間部分。
It's so annoying.
太煩人了。
Does it bug you?
它讓你煩惱嗎？
You bug me.
你煩我。
Is there any chance
有沒有機會
you didn't see that?
你沒看到嗎？
Ross, you gotta stop, okay?
羅斯，你得停下來，好嗎？
You can't just stare through
你不能只是盯著看
the peephole for three hours.
窺視孔三小時。
You're gonna get peep-eyed.
你一定會眼花撩亂。
I knew it. I knew it.
我就知道。我就知道。
I always knew she liked him.
我一直都知道她喜歡他。
You know, she'd say no,
你知道，她會拒絕，
but here we are, right?
但我們到了，對吧？
We just broke up.
我們剛分手。
First thing she does.
她做的第一件事。
You didn't just break up.
你們不是剛分手的。
Hey, it's been, like, three weeks.
嘿，已經過去三個星期了。
You slept with somebody
你和某人睡過
three hours after you thought
在你思考後三小時
you broke up.
你們分手了。
I mean, bullets have left guns slower.
我的意思是，子彈讓槍的速度變慢了。
Here they come. Here they come.
他們來了。他們來了。
Oh, if she kisses him goodnight,
哦，如果她吻他晚安，
I'm gonna kill myself.
我要自殺。
I swear.
我發誓。
I can't. I can't watch.
我不能。我看不下去了
Come on. Date over. Date over.
快點。約會結束。約會結束。
Oh, oh, here we go.
哦，哦，我們開始吧。
She's going in.
她要進去了。
Okay.
好的。
She's going in.
她要進去了。
He's going in.
他要進去了。
The door's closed.
門關著。
I can't see anything,
我什麼也看不見
but the door closed.
但門關著。
And the inventor of the door
還有門的發明者
rests happily in his grave.
幸福地安息在他的墳墓裡。
Okay, I have to do something.
好吧，我必須做點什麼。
I mean, I have to stop it.
我的意思是，我必須阻止它。
Stop what?
停止什麼？
I don't know,
我不知道，
but I have a feeling
但我有一種感覺
that my being there will do it.
我的存在就能做到這一點。
Look, this guy is bad news, Chandler.
聽著，這傢伙是個壞訊息，錢德勒。
He's, I can say,
我可以說他是
he's an operator.
他是一名接線員。
Rachel wouldn't date an operator.
雷切爾不會和接線生約會。
They only make 20 grand a year,
他們一年只賺20英鎊，
and they have to work nights.
他們必須晚上工作。
I'll go over,
我就過去，
and I will borrow something.
我會借點東西。
Juice. I need juice.
汁。我需要果汁。
No, you can't.
不，你不能。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
Look, it must be stuffed.
看看，一定是塞滿了。
I am your friend,
我是你的朋友，
and I am not gonna let you do this.
我不會讓你這麼做的。
You are surprisingly strong.
你出乎意料地堅強。
I need juice.
我需要果汁。
People need juice.
人們需要果汁。
Look, man.
瞧，夥計。
People need juice.
人們需要果汁。
Listen to me.
聽我說。
Juice they need.
他們需要果汁。
She's moving on, okay?
她要繼續前進，好嗎？
If it's not this guy,
如果不是這個人的話
it's gonna be somebody else.
將會是別人。
And unless you're thinking
除非你想
about subletting my people,
關於轉租我的人，
you are gonna have to get used to the fact
你必須要習慣這個事實
that the relationship is over.
關係結束了。
Okay, man?
好吧，夥計？
It's over.
結束了。
Yeah, okay.
是啊，好吧。
Okay.
好的。
It's just I miss her so much.
只是我太想念她了。
I know.
我知道。
Is it just me,
難道只有我一個人，
or did subletting my people
或轉租我的人
sound kind of dirty?
聽起來有點髒？
Why do all your coffee mugs
為什麼你所有的咖啡杯
have numbers on the bottom?
底部有數字嗎？
Uh, that's a Monica complaint.
呃，這是莫妮卡的抱怨。
She can keep track.
她可以跟蹤。
That way, if one of them's missing,
這樣一來，如果其中一個失蹤了，
she can be like,
她可以像，
where's number 27?
27號在哪裡？
You know what?
你知道嗎？
No, and I don't think
不，我不認為
I'm gonna want to.
我會想要。
I can't do this.
我不能這樣做。
Yep, yep.
是的，是的。
That's what I didn't want to know.
這就是我不想知道的。
Yeah, oh, Mark.
是的，哦，馬克。
I'm just doing this
我只是在做這個
for the wrong reasons, you know?
出於錯誤的原因，你知道嗎？
I'm just doing it
我只是在做
to get back at Ross.
去報復羅斯。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
It's not very fair to you.
這對你不太公平。
Ah, fish, man.
啊，魚，夥計。
You know?
你知道？
Look, you want to get back at Ross,
聽著，你想報復羅斯，
I am here for you.
我在這裡等你。
Really.
真的。
No, no.
不，不。
I say, I say,
我說，我說，
I say we get back at him
我說我們要報復他
right here on this couch.
就在這張沙發上。
Right here.
就在這裡。
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
I'm sorry about this.
對此我很抱歉。
That's okay.
沒關係。
You sure?
你確定嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
I could just go home
我可以回家
and get back at him by myself.
然後我自己去報復他。
...to become the penicillin
....成為青黴素
of the 21st century.
21世紀的。
And so today,
所以今天，
this hospital is about
這家醫院是關於
to take major steps
採取重大步驟
toward leading that revolution.
領導這場革命。
It is truly ironic...
實在是太諷刺了…
Hey, can I ask you something?
嘿，我可以問你一件事嗎？
Where are we?
我們在哪裡？
Well,
嗯，
with all these doctors and nurses,
和所有這些醫生和護士一起，
I'm going to say midget rodeo.
我要說的是侏儒牛仔競技表演。
Just tell me the truth.
告訴我真相。
Okay.
好的。
Um,
嗯，
you know,
你知道，
I don't think I told you this,
我想我沒有告訴過你這個
but, um,
但是，嗯，
I just recently got out
我最近才出來
of a really serious relationship.
一段非常認真的關係。
Oh.
哦。
Wasn't that like a year ago?
這不是像一年前那樣嗎？
So I did tell you.
所以我確實告訴過你了。
Okay, well, you know,
好吧，你知道，
that's not really the thing.
事實並非如此。
Um,
嗯，
the thing is,
事情是，
is that right now,
就是現在，
I'm just in a place in my life
我只是在我生命中的一個地方
where I just need to focus on me.
我只需要專注於我自己。
Mm.
毫米。
You know what I mean?
你知道我的意思？
Oh, yeah, I know, yeah.
哦，是的，我知道，是的。
I so want to be attracted to you.
我非常想被你吸引。
But you're not.
但你不是。
Okay, good.
好的，很好。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
Don't be.
別這樣。
Just...
只是...
It's just not...
這只是不...
Don't be,
別這樣，
because it's not so bad.
因為情況還不錯。
It's not?
它不是？
Yeah.
是的。
I know I'm no Jon Bon Jovi.
我知道我不是喬恩·邦·喬維。
Or someone you find attractive.
或者你覺得有吸引力的人。
I'm just...
我只是...
I just think, you know,
我只是想，你知道，
that you might end up
你最終可能會
feeling differently.
感覺不同。
Wow.
哇。
Um, look,
嗯，看，
I don't want this to come out wrong,
我不希望這件事出現錯誤
but, uh,
但是，呃，
you seem awfully confident
你看起來非常有自信
for a guy I just told
對於我剛剛告訴過的一個人
I wasn't attracted to.
我沒有被吸引。
Yeah, stupidly charming, isn't it?
是啊，愚蠢又迷人，不是嗎？
Uh, listen, let's...
呃，聽著，我們...
You want to get something to eat?
你想吃點東西嗎？
Because this place is kind of
因為這個地方有點
depressing.
沉悶。
Well, the man who made
嗯，那個製造了
all this possible,
這一切皆有可能，
Mr. Peter Becker.
彼得貝克爾先生。
One sec.
一秒鐘。
I don't think this town
我不認為這個城市
is big enough
夠大
for the both of us
為了我們倆
to relax in.
放鬆一下。
Draw!
畫！
I wasn't doing anything.
我什麼也沒做。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
What did she do now?
她現在做了什麼？
Just because she went
只因她去了
to Yale Drama.
去耶魯戲劇。
She thinks she's, like,
她認為她就像，
the greatest actress since...
自從...以來最偉大的女演員
since...
自從...
Sliced Bread.
切片麵包。
Ah, Sliced Bread.
啊，切片麵包。
A wonderful Lady Macbeth.
一位出色的麥克白夫人。
God, I just...
天哪，我剛剛...
I hate her.
我討厭她。
I hate her with her...
我討厭她跟她在一起...
Oh, I'm so talented.
哦，我真是太有才了。
And ooh, I'm so pretty.
哦，我真漂亮。
And ooh, I smell so good.
哦，我聞起來很香。
I think somebody
我認為有人
has a crush on somebody.
迷戀某人。
Hey, Chandler,
嘿，錢德勒，
can we please try and stay
我們可以嘗試留下來嗎
focused on my problem here?
專注於我的問題嗎？
You know?
你知道？
I'm talking about you,
我正在談論你，
you big, big freak.
你這個大怪物。
Oh.
哦。
You're out of your mind.
你瘋了。
Hey, you have done nothing
嘿，你什麼也沒做
but talk about her
但談談她
for the last 48 hours.
過去 48 小時。
If you were in a schoolyard,
如果你在校園裡，
you'd be pulling her pigtails
你會拉她的辮子
and pushing her down now.
現在把她推倒了。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是嗎？
Then how come I keep
那我怎麼還留著
thinking about her
想她
in all these sexual scenarios
在所有這些性場景中
and stuff, huh?
還有一些東西，是吧？
Happy?
快樂的？
Is that what I'm supposed
這就是我應該做的嗎
to be, Vic?
維克?
Happy?
快樂的？
Well, why don't you tell me
好吧，為什麼不告訴我
what you're supposed to be?
你應該是什麼？
Huh?
啊？
Because I sure as hell
因為我非常確定
can't figure it out.
想不通。
I talk to you
我跟你說話
and it's nothing.
沒什麼。
You look at me
你看著我
and nothing.
什麼也沒有。
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
You guys make me fly.
你們讓我飛翔。
Hi.
你好。
Okay, we're gonna pick it up
好的，我們去撿起來
here tomorrow.
明天就到這裡。
Well, that was, uh...
嗯，那是，呃...
Better?
更好的？
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, it was definitely
是的，這絕對是
an improvement.
一個改進。
Hi.
你好。
Uh, Kate.
呃，凱特。
Yeah?
是的？
You, uh...
你，呃…
You forgot your shoes.
你忘記穿鞋了。
I'm probably gonna need those, huh?
我可能需要那些，是嗎？
Hey, listen, do you, uh...
嘿，聽著，你是嗎，呃...
Feel like getting a cup of coffee?
想喝杯咖啡嗎？
Um...
嗯...
Kate.
凱特.
You ready to go?
你準備好了嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Very nice.
很不錯。
So, um...
所以，嗯...
See you tomorrow, huh?
明天見，嗯？
Yeah, yeah, sure.
是的，是的，當然。
All right.
好的。
Hey.
嘿。
Why isn't it Spider-Man?
為什麼不是蜘蛛人？
You know, like Goldman, Silverman?
你知道，就像高盛、西爾弗曼一樣？
Because it's not his last name.
因為這不是他的姓。
It isn't?
不是嗎？
No, it's not like...
不，這不像...
Like Phil Spider-Man.
就像菲爾蜘蛛人一樣。
He's a Spider-Man.
他是蜘蛛人。
You know, like, uh...
你知道，就像，呃...
Like Goldman is a last name,
就像高盛是姓氏一樣，
but there's no gold man.
但沒有金人。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
There should be a gold man.
應該有一個金人。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, Rach.
嘿，瑞秋。
How was work?
工作怎麼樣？
Oh, it was great.
哦，太棒了。
Although I did sit down
雖然我確實坐下了
where there wasn't a chair.
那裡沒有椅子。
By the way,
順便說一下，
Ross dropped by a box of your stuff.
羅斯順便拜訪了你的一盒東西。
Oh.
哦。
Well, I guess I had that one coming.
嗯，我想我已經有那個人來了。
Just gonna throw it out.
只是想把它扔掉。
It's probably just a bunch of shampoo and...
可能只是一堆洗髮水...
Something wrong?
有事嗎？
No, nothing.
不，沒什麼。
So, uh,
所以，呃，
what kind of powers would Goldman have?
高盛擁有什麼樣的權力？
Okay, well,
好吧，好吧，
he would turn things to gold.
他會把事情變成金子。
What about things that are already gold?
那些已經是金子的東西怎麼辦？
Ah, his work is done.
啊，他的工作完成了。
Okay, I have a friend,
好吧，我有一個朋友，
Jimmy Tupperman.
吉米·塔珀曼。
What would his powers be?
他的力量是什麼？
Tupperman.
特珀曼。
He would keep criminals fresh
他會讓罪犯保持新鮮感
until the police came.
直到警察來了。
Okay, let's play my game now.
好吧，現在我們來玩我的遊戲吧。
Are you
你是嗎
yellow
黃色
belly
肚子
lily
百合
liver
肝臟
drop?
降低？